<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Horizon</title>
    <description>Welcome to Horizon</description>
    <link>http://horizonapp.co/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://horizonapp.co/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>An Early Birthday Present from Mackenzie Visser</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Today marks my 35th birthday. I received an early birthday present a week ago in the form of an email from a University of Michigan student who found &lt;a href=&quot;https://angel.co/horizon-2/jobs/119322-growth-marketing-marketing-community-intern&quot;&gt;our internship opportunity on AngelList&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Hi Drew,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Yes, I actually just returned to Seattle for the summer from a two month long backpacking trip through Europe. I would say without a doubt it was one of the most influential experiences of my life–I firmly believe that travel is one of the most important experiences a person can have, and I believe that it is key to learning about cultural differences (and similarities).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;I have spent some time looking over the Horizon app and crowdfunding campaign, and I love the concept of Horizon. Of my experiences abroad, the best were by far the places in which I had good accommodations and hosts. It was the Airbnb hostess in Croatia who taught me how to cook traditional scampi and the friends who taught me basic German which made the trip meaningful, not stays in fancy hotels. Traveling this way gave me a much more in depth understanding of the culture I was visiting, as well as lasting connections and friends, and I would recommend it to anyone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;When I talk to my friends at home, the two reasons they say most hold them from traveling back are fear of traveling alone, and money. Horizon provides a solution for both of these issues. By providing trusted connections to stay with, rather than total strangers, I believe many people would feel much more comfortable with the idea of traveling—not only having somewhere safe to stay, but having a friendly face to answer questions and give local recommendations. I also love that Horizon provides affordable accommodations while giving back through charity, simultaneously supporting travel, cultural exchange, and the community.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Traveling is something I hope to do as often as possible throughout the rest of my life, and I would love to be part of a team which helps others to do the same. I am in Seattle for the summer, but would be able to continue working remotely later in the year if possible. Please contact me with more information regarding this position; additionally, please let me know if I can provide any more information. I look forward to hearing from you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Best,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Mackenzie Visser&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s emails like this that keep us committed to Horizon’s &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.horizonapp.co/blog/dina-kaplan-community-accessible/&quot;&gt;mission of unlocking travel opportunities by making community accessible&lt;/a&gt;. Thank you, Mackenzie, for re-affirming the importance of Horizon’s mission – and existence.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://horizonapp.co/blog/early-birthday-present-from-mackenzi-visser/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://horizonapp.co/blog/early-birthday-present-from-mackenzi-visser/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What&#39;s New with Horizon&#39;s Web App</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Though we’ve been quiet here on the blog, we’ve been busy behind the scenes. Our web app recently received an influx of development and design love, and now has the same great ability to filter results by group and accommodation type, or search by city.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our new home screen now supports searching by city:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/blog-horizon-web-app.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can now filter your results by group and accommodation type:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/blog-horizon-web-app-filters.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Design wise, we lightened the whole interface and re-styled all the views. We know there are some who prefer to use our product on the web rather than via a native app. Not everyone has “megs” for that. Finally, travelers using Horizon’s web version can access the same great functionality as those using our iOS and Android versions. A huge thanks goes to &lt;a href=&quot;https://ryanchristo.com/&quot;&gt;Ryan Christoffersen&lt;/a&gt; for all his hard work to make that possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://api.horizonapp.co/&quot; class=&quot;btn btn--full&quot;&gt;Try the Web App Now&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://horizonapp.co/blog/whats-new-web-version/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://horizonapp.co/blog/whats-new-web-version/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Impact Hub Prague Team Visits Seattle</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Back in July, I hosted three of the Impact Hub Prague team – &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/kropacova&quot;&gt;Katerina Kropacova&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/romanbojko&quot;&gt;Roman Bojko&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/pvitek&quot;&gt;Petr Vitek&lt;/a&gt; – who attended the &lt;a href=&quot;http://unlikelyallies.net/&quot;&gt;Unlikely Allies&lt;/a&gt; global gathering at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.impacthubseattle.com/&quot;&gt;Impact Hub Seattle&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/blog-kata-impacthub-2016-07-USA-165.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was certainly a full household in the 2 bedroom, 2 bath condo I share with my roommate in Queen Anne (we were also hosting &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/martinmontero&quot;&gt;Martin Montero&lt;/a&gt;) – so full, in fact, I actually slept at a friends’ house.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We shared drinks (and, yes, shots), meals, and even a morning walk to Pioneer Square from Queen Anne. We made four new friends over the course of those few days, and they all experienced Seattle in an extremely affordable (and fun) way. The gravvy was furhter validating our &lt;a href=&quot;horizonapp.co/blog/travelbygiving-unlock-code/&quot;&gt;#TravelbyGiving&lt;/a&gt; concept with their donation to &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.kiva.org/&quot;&gt;Kiva&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Katerina had the following to say after their stay:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Horizon App is such a amazing piece of work! We have fallen in love with this idea of staying with someone local AND contributing to Kiva in exchange. We will definitely make sure to use it again when we travel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s safe to say community enriches travel opportunities. Thank you to Katerina, Roman, and Petr for sharing Czech culture with me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For attendees of the Unlikely Allies gathering, you may use the group unlock code “unlikelyalliesinsider” if you have an interest in connecting with other attendees around the globe between now and next year’s event in Berlin. Impact Hub members (anywhere), &lt;a href=&quot;&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#116;&amp;#111;:&amp;#115;&amp;#117;&amp;#112;&amp;#112;&amp;#111;&amp;#114;&amp;#116;&amp;#064;&amp;#104;&amp;#111;&amp;#114;&amp;#105;&amp;#122;&amp;#111;&amp;#110;&amp;#097;&amp;#112;&amp;#112;&amp;#046;&amp;#099;&amp;#111;&quot;&gt;shoot us a note&lt;/a&gt; for the private group unlock code to the Hub community.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://horizonapp.co/blog/hub-prague-visits-seattle/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://horizonapp.co/blog/hub-prague-visits-seattle/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Breaking Geographic Silos with Groups</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;One of the regular questions we receive is some iteration of “&lt;em&gt;I’m traveling to Ireland - are there groups I should join for my trip?&lt;/em&gt;”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It seems most people believe groups correspond to geographic locations. I suppose that shouldn’t surprise us, given close to a billion people a month use Facebook groups in that exact way. Couchsurfing groups are generally tied to locations as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a result, I wanted to clarify how you should think about joining and discovering Horizon groups (aka communities).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On Horizon, groups aren’t location specific. Our goal is to remove the geographic silos that exist in virtually every large community, to make global communities more accessible for their members. If you’re a University of Washington alumni (as I am), you should be able to connect with the New York City UW alumni community without having to find and join a separate “UW NYC Alum” group/community. &lt;a href=&quot;/startingbloc/&quot;&gt;StartingBloc Fellows&lt;/a&gt; should be able to connect with fellows in Chicago without the global community having to see the inquiry. &lt;a href=&quot;/startup-chile/&quot;&gt;SUPPERS&lt;/a&gt; should be able to find a Start-up Chile alum in Tokyo without posting a request to the entire global network.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The reason Facebook (and Couchsurfing) groups are organized around locations is the fact they are built around discussions. There is a massive signal to noise challenge any Facebook group with a diverse global diversity inevitably suffers from. Living in Seattle, I don’t care about conversations between members trying to meet in Chicago or Beijing or Capetown – but I do care about anyone coming to Seattle. Most members are not willing to sort through 99% noise, for the 1% signal they care about (in my case, people coming to Seattle). We’re not building an app to enable community members to “talk” to each other; there are plenty of ways to do that already. We’re building the most efficient way to find trusted individuals by location – which means being a member of communities such as &lt;a href=&quot;/sigma-phi-epsilon/&quot;&gt;SigEp&lt;/a&gt; means being a member across all geographies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How do you get a group unlock code for a community to which you belong you ask? From a member already in the group.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Questions, or want a new group created? &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:support@horizonapp.co&quot;&gt;Drop us a line.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note:&lt;/strong&gt; There are a number of “public” groups you may join using our &lt;a href=&quot;http://api.horizonapp.co/groups/&quot;&gt;web&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;/android/&quot;&gt;Android&lt;/a&gt; version, and will be available in iOS soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://horizonapp.co/blog/breaking-geographic-silos-groups/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://horizonapp.co/blog/breaking-geographic-silos-groups/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>To My Fellow AIESEC Members – The Ones I Love and the Ones I Have yet to Meet</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;As an international nonprofit, &lt;a href=&quot;http://aiesec.org/&quot;&gt;AIESEC&lt;/a&gt; aims to increase cross cultural exchange and awareness. The urgency of this mission is evident. One tragedy after the next, we are reminded that a  fundamental lack of understanding between cultures and people exists. As active members or alumni, we are devoted to creating a more connected and accepting world. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are united by a similar vision for this world – aligned in our mindset. And this is exactly why this community is so important to me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now here’s what Horizon can do for us and our community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Right now, I see so many lost connections. Horizon’s app gives us the opportunity to connect with more AIESEC members across the globe, strengthen our community, and enable authentic travelling experiences – by bringing transparency to the locations of the AIESEC global community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Horizon is not about building a new community for us. Our AIESEC community already exists, yet we can’t even begin to grasp the reach and potential of our community. There are chapters in over 125 countries and we have served over 1,000,000 individuals in the past seven decades. We are spread all over the world, yet our shared mindset has led us to become a part of one remarkable community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Horizon connects us to people in our trusted community. The app resembles our CouchSurfing group on Facebook. Though utilized by more than 18k, the group quickly gets overwhelming with a constant stream of notifications, eventually losing its original intent. Horizon aims to efficiently connect travelers to potential hosts. The app tells us who in any given location has the capacity to host, while also giving us the opportunity to host travelers in our space. It allows us to welcome people into our place or let others introduce us to the little quirks of the place they come from.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyone who has ever stayed with friends or hosts during their travels recognizes that the experience is inherently unique – full of genuine connections and unforgettable stories. Staying in a hotel or an Airbnb is just not the same.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Download Horizon on your &lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/horizon-app-travel-stay-people/id960391979?mt=8&quot;&gt;iPhone&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.horizonapp.co/android/&quot;&gt;Android&lt;/a&gt; and let’s connect.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re a member of AIESEC or an alumni and would like to join &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.horizonapp.co/AIESEC/&quot;&gt;the AIESEC group on Horizon&lt;/a&gt;, please contact me at alinalkm@uw.edu. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://horizonapp.co/blog/to-my-fellow-AIESEC-members-the-ones-I-love-and-the-ones-I-have-yet-to-meet/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://horizonapp.co/blog/to-my-fellow-AIESEC-members-the-ones-I-love-and-the-ones-I-have-yet-to-meet/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Real Estate Learnings Applied to Vacation Rentals</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Similarities between marketing a real estate property and marketing a vacation rental property run deep (some of you may know my previous professional experience is in the real estate industry). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Where you rest your head at night is the consumer building block both the real estate and travel industries are built upon, as well as the primary monetization catalyst.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Especially if you’re a host/owner of a vacation rental (or shared room on AirBnB), you may find value in the guest post I wrote for &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.coral.life/&quot;&gt;Coral&lt;/a&gt; applying some of my learnings from real estate to vacation rentals. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.coral.life/2016/05/23/real-estate-and-vacation-rentals/&quot; class=&quot;btn btn--full&quot;&gt;Read Now&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://horizonapp.co/blog/real-estate-learnings-applied-vacation-rentals/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://horizonapp.co/blog/real-estate-learnings-applied-vacation-rentals/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Two Media Mentions, and Context on Horizon&#39;s Long Term Vision</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Most entrepreneurs believe there is a “&lt;em&gt;wrong&lt;/em&gt;” in the world, and they are the ones that need to “&lt;em&gt;right&lt;/em&gt;” it. For me, that wrong is the very real life lottery that exists in this world, which is as simple as where you’re born. From my point of view, access to community is the only way to break that cycle and lesson the opportunity/income inequality that exists worldwide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For further clarity on the longer term vision (and some of what got us to this point), there are two recent media hits worth noting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An interview in the Huffington Post (conducted by &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/ioanablog&quot;&gt;Ioana Budeanu&lt;/a&gt;):&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://huffingtonpost.com/entry/drew-meyers-conversations-friendships-experiences_us_57369f2fe4b0ed0ca07a9295&quot; class=&quot;btn btn--full&quot;&gt;Read Now&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A podcast interview with Tony Loyd on the &lt;a href=&quot;http://tonyloyd.com/category/podcast/&quot;&gt;Social Entrepreneur Podcast&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.tonyloyd.com/076-2/&quot; class=&quot;btn btn--full&quot;&gt;Listen Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hope the combination of the two helps bring clarity to the long term vision of Horizon, and why enabling community worldwide is so vital. Thanks for the continued support.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://horizonapp.co/blog/media-hits-horizon-vision/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://horizonapp.co/blog/media-hits-horizon-vision/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Android is Ready for Open Testing</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We recently &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.producthunt.com/tech/horizon-for-android&quot;&gt;announced our open Android beta on Product Hunt&lt;/a&gt;. The big product change is that we now &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.horizonapp.co/blog/sublet-support/&quot;&gt;support posting and finding sublets&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/product-hunt-logo-1.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The app is fully functional – but is lacking welcome &amp;amp; first time onboarding screens, as well as design polish.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://play.google.com/apps/testing/co.horizonapp.horizonapp&quot; class=&quot;btn btn--full&quot;&gt;Download&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’d love to hear from the Android population out there. &lt;a href=&quot;&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#116;&amp;#111;:&amp;#115;&amp;#117;&amp;#112;&amp;#112;&amp;#111;&amp;#114;&amp;#116;&amp;#064;&amp;#104;&amp;#111;&amp;#114;&amp;#105;&amp;#122;&amp;#111;&amp;#110;&amp;#097;&amp;#112;&amp;#112;&amp;#046;&amp;#099;&amp;#111;&quot;&gt;Email&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.twitter.com/gethorizonappco&quot;&gt;Tweet your feedback&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://horizonapp.co/blog/android-open-testing/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://horizonapp.co/blog/android-open-testing/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Long Term Societal Danger of Screen Addiction</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;A week in Cuba with absolutely zero internet for 7 days made me re-realize the reality that screen addiction doesn’t exist everywhere. Yet. All the time people in the developed world spend browsing Twitter, Facebook, Buzzfeed, People Magazine, and TMZ – as well as countless hours indulging in Netflix, Hulu, and Showtime – people in Cuba (&amp;amp; most other places in the developing world) spend actually talking to each other, strengthening relationships &amp;amp; helping each other. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s no wonder their sense of community is so much stronger than ours. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Based on &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.horizonapp.co/blog/why-horizon-exists/&quot;&gt;our why&lt;/a&gt;, it’s probably no surprise I don’t believe whether a world experienced face to face is better than a world experienced through a screen is a point of discussion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If the current global trend toward more and more time spent on your phone/tablet/computer/tv continues unopposed to the rest of the world, we’re headed toward a dangerously soulless, lonely world. Building community in the physical world, one interaction &amp;amp; one friendship at a time, is the only way to slow down or reverse that trend toward screen addiction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why does community matter to you? &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.twitter.com/gethorizonappco&quot;&gt;Tweet us your response&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PS #1: &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2014/oct/14/age-of-loneliness-killing-us?CMP=share_btn_tw&quot;&gt;The age of loneliness is killing us&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, an article published in the Guardian in 2014, may provide additional useful context.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PS #2: I also encourage you to watch “&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GXdVPLj_pIk&quot;&gt;Are you living the life that you post?&lt;/a&gt;”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/GXdVPLj_pIk&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://horizonapp.co/blog/long-term-societal-danger-screen-addiction/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://horizonapp.co/blog/long-term-societal-danger-screen-addiction/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Horizon for AirBnB Hosts</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;As a result of our latest product changes allowing hosts to provide a text description and link to an external website, we believe there is a compelling proposition for existing hosts on AirBnB (and other vacation rental &amp;amp; homestay platforms) to use Horizon as a complementary tool:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Help your trusted network discover your listing, book direct, and perhaps get a discount (hosts we&#39;ve spoken to give 10-25% off to those in their network).&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Indicate your willingness to rent for a longer period of time and allow travelers interested in that scenario to book direct once you assess trust (&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.horizonapp.co/blog/sublet-support/&quot;&gt;more on sublet support here&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Avoid dealing with inquiries from strangers.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Get more inquires from people who share your interests (such as skiing, diving, social enterprise, EDM, etc). You can find numerous &lt;a href=&quot;http://api.horizonapp.co/groups/&quot;&gt;public groups on our web version&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:info@horizonapp.co&quot;&gt;email us&lt;/a&gt; if you want a new group created.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Feedback and suggestions are welcome. You can reach us at &lt;a href=&quot;&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#116;&amp;#111;:&amp;#115;&amp;#117;&amp;#112;&amp;#112;&amp;#111;&amp;#114;&amp;#116;&amp;#064;&amp;#104;&amp;#111;&amp;#114;&amp;#105;&amp;#122;&amp;#111;&amp;#110;&amp;#097;&amp;#112;&amp;#112;&amp;#046;&amp;#099;&amp;#111;&quot;&gt;&amp;#115;&amp;#117;&amp;#112;&amp;#112;&amp;#111;&amp;#114;&amp;#116;&amp;#064;&amp;#104;&amp;#111;&amp;#114;&amp;#105;&amp;#122;&amp;#111;&amp;#110;&amp;#097;&amp;#112;&amp;#112;&amp;#046;&amp;#099;&amp;#111;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://horizonapp.co/blog/airbnb-hosts-vacation-rentals/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://horizonapp.co/blog/airbnb-hosts-vacation-rentals/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
